(忆往昔)
小心了 天使们
Watch you angels.
没有人能够幸存
No one will survive this one.
这是场灾难
It's madness.
我的名字是Bartholomew
It's Bartholomew.
所以说天使们都是混蛋
And now we said the angels are dicks.
他是谁
What is that.
Kevin Tran
It's Kevin Tran.
原本只是个优等生
Who was a good straight A kid.
却被卷进了这里
And then he got sucked in.
这些天使的烂摊子
All this this angel crap.
他成了先知
He became a prophet.
我不想做先知
I don't wanna be a prophet.
妈妈
Hi,mama.
你折磨我
You tortured me.
我对我的朋友都这么干
I tortured all my friends.
你杀了我妈妈
You killed my mom.
哦 是吗
Did I.
伙计 我们告诉过你不要和Crowley交谈 好吗
Man,we told you not to talk to Crowley,okay.
他会扰乱你的思想
He messes with your head.
这是你名单上要除掉的第一个人
Here's the first name on your to do list.
不
No.
Kevin不可能全身而退
There is no way that Kevin getting out of this intact.
对吗
Is there.
你必须要相信我
You need to trust me.
我总是相信你
I always trust you.
最后事情却总是一团糟
And always end up screwed.
你救我 并不是为了我
You didn't save me,for me.
你这样做是为你自己
You did it,for you.
你不想一个人
You don't wanna be alone.
如果当时我们俩情况对调
If the situation were reversed.
换做是我奄奄一息 你也会为我做同样的事
And I was dying,you'd do the same thing.
不 Dean 我不会的
No,Dean.I wouldn't.
如今
Now.
Sam
Sam.
Dean
Dean.
所以
So.
是的 地堡里闹鬼了
Yep,bunker is haunted.
这怎么可能
How is this possible.
你不是说这里是地球上最安全的地方吗
Thought you said it's the safest place on the planet.
听着 我知道肯定没有东西能进来
Look,I know nothing got in.
我是说地堡
I mean the bunker is warded and sigiled.
从里到外都做了防护措施
From top to bottom.
没东西能从外面闯进来
There is no way that something came in from outside.
好吧 那么这个鬼魂 肯定是死在这里面的
OK,so whoever is haunting us,died here.
什么 是死去的学者吗
What,died Man of Letters.
不 这说不通
No,that doesn't track.
我们是五十年来
I know we are the first people.
第一次住进这里的人
That occupied this place in fifty years.
这个鬼魂为何等了这么久才出来吓唬人
Why would a ghost wait for so long to get a spook on.
比较有可能是Kevin
Eh,must have been more reasonable with Kevin.
不可能
No.
你怎么能这么确定
How can you be so sure.
因为是我亲自火化了他的尸体
Because I burned his body myself,okay.
绝对不是他
It's not him.
好吧 你烧了他的尸体
OK,so you cremated him.
但是我们也烧了Bobby的尸体 他不也回来了
We cremated Bobby,too.He came back.
够了 我告诉你
That's it,I'm telling you.
这个鬼魂 绝对不是Kevin
This ghost is not Kevin.
Kevin
Kevin.
我们将躯体交予大地
We commit our body to the ground.
尘归尘 土归土
Earth to earth,ashes to ashes,dust to dust.
带着清晰坚定的希望
With a clear and certain hope.
希望能拥有永恒的来生
Of the resurrection unto the eternal life.
依照上帝伟大的造诣
According to mighty working.
我们因为他而拥有宁静
We are by his able to subdue all things up to himself.
你在这里干什么
What're you doing here.
他是我的朋友
He used to be my friend.
谁 那个人类还是
Who?The dead human or.
附身她时被杀的天使
The angel who's killed while possessing her.
天使
The angel.
Rebecca
Rebecca.
Rebecca有不少朋友
Rebecca had a lot of friends.
比如像Metatron一样的朋友
Friends like Metatron.
他在哪里
Where is he.
你恐怕找错地方了
You are looking in the wrong place.
Rebecca和Metatron曾经是朋友
Rebecca and Metatron were friends.
但那是很久之前的事了
That was a long time ago.
自从坠落之后就再无联络了
Had no contact since the fall.
Naomi Metatron 天堂的战役 还有那些权利争夺
Naomi,Metatron,heavenly battles,politics.
她都放弃了
She gave it up.
放弃了所有
All of it.
Rebecca告诉我们 作为天使
Rebecca taught us the angels have lost touch.
我们已经遗失了自己真正的使命
With our true missions.
你说我们是什么意思
What do you mean by us.
那些忏悔者
The penitents.
她的追随者
Her followers.
又是一个帮派
Another faction.
和其他的不同
Not like the others.
我们不会挑起战争
We don't make war.
我们谦卑地生活在人类之中
We live humbly among these humans.
但我们现在已经暴露了
Or we did.
他杀了其他所有的人
He killed all the others.
然后杀了她
And he killed her.
谁杀了她
Who did.
还能是谁
Who else.
那个怪物 Bartholomew
The monster,Bartholomew.
有什么发现
Anything.
这玩意儿叮了几声 探测仪有了点儿反应
A couple of dings,a little EMF activity.
但是就没有其他的动静了
But mostly silence.
所以他暂时躲回屏障里了
So he is back in the veil.
我想是的
I guess so.
摸索着等待时机再次现身
Fumbling to break through.
要知道上次Bobby花了几个月才成功的
You got to figure it took Bobby months to make contact.
Kevin只是 他有这方面的知识
Kevin's only...he is knew of these.
是啊 好吧 该你值班了
Right,alright you're up.
Kevin
Kevin.
好吧 我干不下去了
Alright,I can't do this.
咖啡机半夜乱响什么的
Coffee buzzing bump in the night crap.
我有很重要的事情要跟你说
I got serious thing to say to you.
我绝不会对着这玩意说的
And I'm not gonna saying them to this.
Kevin 我很抱歉
Kevin I'm sorry.
这不是你想要的生活
You do not choose this life.
你努力拼命过
You busted your ass.
但是却失去了所有 所有你爱的人
You lost everything,everyone you loved.
最后你得到了什么呢
And your reward.
连自己的性命也没能保住
Getting killed.
我本该好好保护你
On my watch.
如果我
If I...
这都是我的错
It was on me.
是我的错让你
It was my fault that.
现在我做什么都无济于事了
There is nothing I can do to make that right.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
嘿 你看见这个了吗
Hey,did you see this.
灯光怎么
The lights were.
不是吧
This not happening.
费劲巴拉花了好几个月
Did not spend months struggling.
冲破屏障
To break through the veil.
出来之后不但动不了
Just to get stuck in listening Dean Winchester.
还得听Dean Winchester自怨自艾
Having a self-pity session.
我活着的时候
Didn't hear enough of those.
那些话就已经听了无数遍了好吗
When I was alive.
Kevin
Kevin.
你们能看见我了吗
You can see me.
放松点 Kevin
Take it easy,Kevin.
最开始你可能维持不了多久
You might not hold this one for too long.
你需要时间练习
It takes a while.
那么我们应该长话短说
And we should talk fast.
你不应该在天堂吗
Why aren't you in heaven.
你是最应该进天堂的那个人啊
I mean if anybody deserves an express pass to paradise.
不 我去不了天堂
No,I couldn't,I can't.
没人能进
No one can.
天堂天堂关门大吉了
Heaven has closed for business.
天使们堕天之后 所有死去的人
Everyone who's died since angels fell.
都只能卡在屏障之后 等待着
Just stuck in the veil,waiting.
而且这里糟糕透了
And it's bad in here.
就跟在车管所排长队一样糟糕
Like DMV-Line-Times-Infinity bad.
我们能做些什么
What can we do.
我需要帮忙 帮我一个大忙
I need a favor,a big one.
好的
Okay.
找到我妈妈
Find my mother.
Kevin
Kevin.
Crowley告诉你她还活着
Crowley only told you she is alive.
只是为了扰乱你的思想
To mess with you.
我没有听信他的话
I'm not going off his words.
我有自己的消息来源
And I have my own sources.
这里十分拥挤
It's crowd in the field.
所有人都被困在这个世界里等待真正的死亡
All of us stuck in the other side for death.
但是我能够得到和传递一些信息
But I've been able to pass the messages.
在鬼魂之间
Spirit to spirit.
我和一个新来的鬼魂取得了联系
I made contact with another new arrival.
她说她见过我妈 就在一周之前
She said she saw my mom just a week ago.
她还活着
Alive.
好吧 但是跟你对话的这个鬼魂
Okay,this spirit that you ghost telephone with.
你甚至连她是谁都不知道
You wouldn't even know about her.
她名字叫Candy
Her name is Candy.
她说她在威奇托市的一处森林里
She said she's in a forest in Wichita.
Candy
Candy.
所以这就是所有你知道的信息了
That's it,that's all you got.
那里的长距离通话质量
Long distance communication within the veil.
可不怎么理想
Is not ideal.
所以我需要你们过去看一看
That's why I need you go there.
召唤她
Summon her.
看看她还知道些什么
See what else she knows.
你说你想要弥补过错
You say you wanna make it right.
这就是个机会
This is how.
你的朋友这么急匆匆的是要去哪儿啊
Where is your friend going in such a hurry.
你来晚了 他已经走了
You're too late.He's gone.
Castiel
Castiel.
我们头儿找你有一阵子了
Our boss'been looking for you.
威奇托市 堪萨斯州
Wichita Kansas.
我们到了 这就是那座桥
All right,that's the trestle.
Kevin说那个鬼魂就被困在这附近
Kevin said the spirit was stuck nearby.
她是在这儿死的吗
She died here.
是啊
Yeah.
她是被什么东西杀死的 熊吗
What got her,a bear.
我们居然要召唤一只叫Candy的鬼魂
I'm still stuck in the fact that.
我还是没法消化这事儿
We're trying to summon a ghost named Candy.
事先声明 Kevin说
You know just 'cause Kevin said.
他听到他妈妈还活着
That he heard his mom's alive.
并不代表她还
Doesn't mean she.
嘿 这件事怎么说也是我们欠他的
Hey,at least we owe this kid a try,right.
你都带了些什么
What did you bring.
既然她死了才一周左右
Well,she's not only been dead for a week.
我想
Right,so I figured.
她一定迫不及待地想出来
She could use as much help as she can get.
所以
So.
认真的吗
Really.
不能放过任何一个机会
Whatever works.
我还要再等多久
How much longer.
你这么着急是要去哪儿
You have some place to be.
他的刃
His blade.
我们也是按安全协议办事
Standard security protocol.
这年头还是万事小心为妙
Can't be too careful these days.
你好 Bartholomew
Hello,Bartholomew.
Castiel
Castiel.
真是太久没见了
It has been too long.
你感觉到了吗
You feel that.
我有点儿起鸡皮疙瘩了
I think I felt the chill.
是啊
Yeah.
因为这儿很冷
It's because it's cold.
Crowley 我是Dean
Crowley,This is Dean.
给我回个电话
Call me when you get this.
说真的 Dean
Really?Dean.
怎么了
What.
这已经是你第三次转到他的语音信箱了
It's your third unanswered voicemail.
你有没有想过 可能他对你不感兴趣了
Have you ever think maybe he's just not that into you.
他是我们手上最后一个指向Tran夫人的可靠线索
Well,he's our last confirmed link to Mrs.Tran.
我承认他是个杀千刀的混蛋
Yes,he's a flaming douche.
但是至少他是个大活人
But at least we know he's real which is more.
比这个不见踪影的Candy靠谱多了
Than we can say of this Candy-No-Show.
有人吗
Hello.
- Candy - 有人吗
- Candy - Hello.
是你吗 是你吗 Candy
Are you there?Is that you,Candy.
有人吗
Hello.
真是疯狂啊 是不是
Madness,wasn't it.
20个天使退居战线之后
A peer your force of twenty behind the enemy lines.
跟Raphael
Launching and encouraging.
和他的手下开战
Against Raphael and his loyalists.
那是预料中的风险
It was a calculated risk.
我一度以为你失去了理智
I thought you've gone insane.
对你的领导能力提出质疑
I questioned your leadership.
对派给我的任务疑虑不定
Second guess every step that I campaigned.
但你是我的指挥官
But you're my commander.
我缄默不言 按命令行事
I held my tongue,I followed orders.
Raphael逃跑了
Raphael fled.
他的追随者们不是死了就是被囚
Most of his loyalists died or captured.
你的险冒对了 你
Your gamble paid off.You.
你赢了
Won.
我们赢了
We won.
我们听到了你胜利的消息
We've heard your victory spread.
你又被召回戍卫队
You got called back to the garrison.
成为了 伟大的Castiel
You became The Great Castiel.
那时我只是个低等兵而已
While I stay behind just a grunt.
你 也为自己闯出了一番名声
You gained reputation for yourself as well.
我把俘虏交给你看管
The captives I left in your care.
可是你 残忍的折磨并杀害了他们
You tortured and killed them.
我只是服从命令杀掉他们而已
I was ordered to kill those captives.
你已经脱离天堂太久了
You've been flying solo for so long.
忘记了天使的义务
You've forgotten that's what angels do.
我们服从命令
We follow orders.
但你却没有
Not you though.
你不会再服从命令了
Not anymore.
没错
That's right.
现在我是发号施令的人
I give them.
等等
Hang on.
就是那儿 就是那儿 停停停
There,there,there.Stop,stop,stop.
Candy
Candy.
在盒子里 他们把我关在盒子里
In a box.They put me in a box.
我们所有人都在盒子里
All of us in boxes.
一个挨着一个 我 Gerome 还有Linda
Side by side,me,Gerome,Linda.
- Linda是 - Tran太太
- Linda's - Mrs.Tran.
Candy 那些盒子 你知道它们在哪儿吗
Candy,these boxes,where were they.
我不知道
I don't know.
这儿很冷
Here's cold.
一片漆黑
Dark.
后面有一个小铁窗
There was a back chain.
我们彼此能说话
We can talked to one another.
好吧 墙壁
Okay the walls.
你能描述一下墙壁和地面的样子吗
Can you describe them.
光滑
Bare.
水泥地
Cement.
但是门 门是金属的
Except for the door,that was...metal.
而且 凹凸不平
But...like,ridged.
凹凸不平
Ridged.
你是说有波浪弧度吗
You mean like corrugated.
是的
Yeah.
我试过抬门 没抬起来
I tried to lift the door but I couldn't.
门从外面被锁上了
Locked from the outside.
仓库
Like a storage unit.
有可能
Maybe.
Candy
Candy.
你知道是谁在看着你们吗
Who was holding you there.
有两个人
Two men.
这里太黑了
There're so dark in the box.
他们进来的时候 强光刺得我睁不开眼
When they came,I can barely see.
最先走进来的那个 我觉得是个英国人
The first guy...was British I think.
矮矮的
Kind of short.
说话都是说给自己听
Love hearing himself talk.
是Crowley
Crowley.
他们的目的是什么
And what do they want.
说我活着比死了更有价值
Said I was worth more alive than dead.
但后来他突然就不来了
But he stopped coming.
另外一个人继续来查看我们的情况
Then it was just...the other guy.
我们以为就剩他一个人
We thought it was just him.
我们想逃跑
We tried to escape.
我使劲地跑 能跑多远跑多远
I ran so hard...so far.
但是
But.
Candy
Candy.
Candy你还在吗
Candy,you there.
Tran太太怎么样了
What about Mrs.Tran.
Candy
Candy.
我不知道
I don't know.
她也许还活着
Maybe she survived.
什么叫也许
Maybe.
你跟她儿子可不是这么说的
That's not what you told her son.
我说我们在一起的时候她还活着
I said she was alive.
但后来发生了什么我就不知道了
I don't know what happened after.
但我宁愿她死了
For her sake,I hope she died.
不要
No.
附近有三处仓库
Okay there're 3 storage facilities nearby.
最近的一个离这里大概有1英里
The closest one is about a mile on the road.
另外 我去查了查Candy的资料
And I...I dug up some stuff on Candy.
发现她被一个位高权重的
Turns out she was the kept women of the.
议员包养了
Powerful congressman.
有小道媒体称
Gossip blog said.
他恨不得舔遍她走过的每一寸土地
He worshiped the ground she walked on.
真的是舔
Literally.
他有恋足癖
He had foot fetish.
所以Crowley绑架了
So Crowley was holding the.
一个高官深爱的美女
Beloved tootsies of powerful politician.
还有一个先知深爱的妈妈
And the beloved mother of the powerful prophet.
他们是他的砝码
Human leverage.
但为什么要杀了Candy
Why killed Candy.
你也听到她的话了
You heard her.
她想要逃跑
She tried to make a break for it.
也许Crowley是想杀鸡儆猴
Maybe Crowley wanted to make an example.
不
Nah.
不 是留下的负责人这么想
No,the guy left in charge.
Crowley更希望他的人质们都好好活着
Crowley wanted the victims alive.
怎么 你想给他颁发个好人勋章吗
So,what,you want to give him a metal.
说到底 Crowley才是最初
I mean,Crowley's the one.
把他们囚禁起来的那个人
Who put them into the cells in the first place.
是啊 我知道
Yeah,I know.
我只是摆出事实
I'm just talking it out,you know.
梳理案情
Working the case.
公事公办
Businesslike.
后来我们发现这些人的实际用处并不大
Realizing they have more trouble than they were worth.
于是我们就清除了这群人类帮手
We purged our human allies.
征用了Boyle教友会
Then commanded Boyle Ministry,Inc.
从此自己用
For our own use.
Boyle神父
Buddy Boyle.
你杀了他
So you killed him.
不
No.
我们把他和他的同伴变成了容器
We made him and his colleagues vessels.
留下了那些能承受的住的
At least,those who didn't go pop.
你很紧张吗 Castiel
You nervous,Castiel.
你的追随者都想让我死
Your followers want me dead.
我不确定你是不是也这么想
I'm not entirely certain you don't too.
如果我想要你死
If I wanted you dead.
你早就死了
You'd be dead.
所以我们是朋友了
So we're friends here.
是的
Yes.
那我能随时离开这里了
And I'm free to go.
当然
Of course.
虽然我不认为你有离开的理由
Though I don't know why you would.
外面到底有什么 Castiel
What's out there for you Castiel.
凭你一个人 你能干成什么大事吗
What do you really expect to accomplish on your own.
你自己永远不可能找到Metatron
You'll never find Metatron that way.
你怎么知道Metatron
How did you know about Metatron.
我猜你之所以追着Rebecca不放
I figured that's why you're persuing Rebecca.
找上她的追随者 都是因为这个
Engaging with her follower.
也许我们处事的方式不同 Cass
We have different methods,Cass.
但我们的目标是一样的
But we want the same thing.
找到Metatron 让所有天使回天堂
To find Metatron and restore our kind to heaven.
那你为什么杀了Rebecca和她的追随者
Then why kill Rebecca and her followers.
他们并不对你构成威胁
They're not threat to you.
可能吧
Perhaps.
但相比于放任自然
But better to nip a fledgling faction in the bud.
我还是更喜欢防患于未然
Than let it grow into a bigger threat down on the road.
用最小的牺牲 拯救更多的生命
A drop of blood to save a gallon.
我不同意
I don't agree.
我不是在征求你的同意
I'm not asking you to.
抓捕Metatron 我比Malachi那队快
I will outrace Malachi in the hunt for Metatron.
我肯定也比你一个人快
And I will certainly outrace you on your own.
但如果你能接受我的战略
But if you can set aside your qualms.
跟我合作的话
About methods for one second.
打倒Metatron并不成问题
There's no reason the two of us can't take him down.
我们两个一起
Together.
我猜这个人一米七不到 肤色惨白
Let me guess 5'5",pasty white.
黑框嬉皮士眼镜 和上个地方那个人一样
Black-rimmed hipster glasses,just like the last place.
全对
Nailed it.
有什么可以帮助您的
Can I help you.
你好 我们是探员Nicks和McVie
Yeah,hi.Agents Nicks and McVie.
可以看下你们的租赁记录吗
Mind if I take a look at your rental records.
我经理不在这 我觉得我不该
My manager is not here.I really don't think I should.
嘿 快拿记录来 伙计
Hey,the records,pal.
Barry
Barry.
把租赁记录活页夹拿出来
Bring out the rental binder.
这个就是 先生
Here you go,sir.
看这个
Hey,check it out.
走廊Q
Corridor Q.
三个并排单元 和其它的分离
Three adjacent units,separated from the others.
Candy说有三个人质 对吧
I mean Candy said there were three hostages,right.
这三个都租给了同一个人
OK,it's all leased by the same guy.
叫D Webster
A D Webster.
D Webster
D Webster.
是Daniel Webster的缩写吗
Well,as in like Daniel Webster.
我觉得这不像是Crowley开的低级玩笑
Well,I know a lame Crowley in-joke when I see one.
你们说D Webster吗
You guys say D Webster.
是的 你见过他吗
Yeah.You've seen him.
不 只是
No,it's just.
我知道这是记录上登记的名字
I know it's a name from the records.
他在我们仓库的另一边
He's leasing another unit.
也租了一个房间
On the other side of the facility.
我可以带你们去看看
I can show you.
好 太好了
Yeah,that would be great.
那么 你查一下走廊Q
All right.Why don't you take corridor Q.
我和这个升级版Del一起过去看看
I'm going with the Del the funky homosapien.
Tran女士
Mrs.Tran.
Mrs.Tran,hey hey hey.
是我 Sam
It's me.It's Sam.
你没事了
I got you.
Sam
Sam.
我们得逃出去
We have to get out of here.
他马上就回来了
Before he comes back.
Kevin和你一起吗
Is Kevin with you.
你确定这间借给Webster了吗
You sure this is the one leased by Webster.
是的 就是这间
Yeah, this is it
(收件地址是Sam和Dean在堪萨斯的老家)
你确定这儿的主人不是Crowley吗
This isn't in Crowley's unit.
这些坐标是什么
What are these locations.
Metatron出现过的地方
Sightings of Metatron.
他最近来过地球吗
He's been on earth.
据我们所知有三次
Three times we know of so far.
这就是大规模地面行动的好处
That's the benefit of a massive ground operation.
到处都有我们的眼线
Eyes and ears,everywhere.
我们不久
It's only a matter of time.
就能知道他的实时位置了
Before we get an active location.
为什么还要等
Why wait.
有了这些信息 我可以引他出来
With this kind of information I'd lure him out.
我就知道你的利用价值很高
I knew you would be an asset.
你才是最想整垮他的人
No one is as motivated as you to take him down.
跟其他天使集团的争斗让我忙得不可开交
I had my hands so full with the factions.
导致我无法一心完成主要目标
It has distracted me from the real goal.
但是有了你在身边
But with you by my side.
新老板和终极叛党携手合作
The new boss and the ultimate rebel working together.
这会让那些
Think of the message that.
想叛变的天使怎么想
Would send to the would-be dissidents.
他们肯定会明白 反抗只会是徒劳
They'd finally understand that resistance is futile.
想想我们会避免多少流血事件
Think of the bloodshed we could avert.
想想团结一心的天使们
What a united angel kind.
在天堂或者其它地方会有怎样的
Could accomplish in heaven.
成就
Elsewhere.
Barth 你在做什么
Barth,what are you doing.
做该做的事
What needs to be done.
我要折磨这个叛徒
I'm gonna torture the rebel.
逼问他
Find out what he knows.
然后杀了他
Then kill him.
你要协助我
And you are going to help.
开了
There you go.
好了
All right.
有条电线连着控制板
There's an electrical line leads to the control panel.
恐怕得花点时间
Okay,this might take a while.
先要把接地线关了
We have to unplug the ground wire first.
如果这是标准美式色彩编码
If this is standard US color-coding.
就应该是绿色的线
It should be the green one.
好吧
Okay.
我之前帮Kevin做过工程俱乐部的作业
Helping Kevin with his engineering club assignments.
学会了一两招
I've picked up a thing or two.
我知道他肯定闹着要来
I'm sure he insisted.
不过我相信你们没有蠢到
But I trust you weren't foolish enough.
带他一起来执行这种任务
To bring Kevin along on this mission.
所以把他留在了一个安全的地方
That you left him somewhere safe.
当然
Of course.
很好
Good.
我们只要打开这扇门
Now all we have to do is get this door open.
逃出去
Get the hell out of here.
你们就能让我见着我儿子了
And you'll bring me to my son.
Tran夫人
Listen,Ms.Tran.
你们一定要带我去见我儿子
You will take me to my son.
手电筒
Flashlight.
他当时说 相信我
Trust me,he says.
你肯定会想加入这个行动的
You definitely want to be a part of this.
这是个了解我事业的基础的机会
A chance to get in on the ground floor of my operation.
一次学习经验的机会
A real learning experience.
就把它当做垫脚石 孩子
Consider it a stepping stone,my lad.
和实习一样
Like an internship.
早就该知道 实习都是见鬼的
Should have known,internship suck.
所以 就是你了
So,you're the one.
Corwley任命的负责人
You're the one Crowley left in charge.
是的 多么荣幸啊
Yeah,what a privilege.
喂养猿人
Feeding the apes.
拖地板
Hosing the floors.
洗粪桶
Washing up honey buckets.
什么好处都没有
For zero credit.
老板 不知去向
The boss,MIA.
地位太重要 不能来上班
Too important to show for work.
连接下我的电话都不行
To even return my calls.
但是 最惨的是
But,you know the worst part.
我竟然不能杀人
I wasn't even allowed to kill anyone.
而要保护他们
I was told to protect them.
太变态了吧
I mean how sick is that.
我也是个年轻力壮的恶魔啊
Am I not a young vital demon.
我也有基本需求啊
With basic demon needs.
也有我的权利
And rights.
而我传话给Crowley
And when I call Crowley to inform him.
说我单枪匹马地抓住了Winchester兄弟
That I've single-handedly caught the Winchesters.
就算他接了我电话
If he even answers my call.
估计我连一声谢谢都听不到
Think I'll get a thank you.
你说的对 年轻人
You're right,kid.
他不但不会感谢你
He won't give you credit.
还会生你气
If anything,he'll be pissed.
什么
What.
我和Crowley 我们
Well,me and Crowley,we're.
我们关系很好
We're tight now.
铁哥们儿
Thick as thieves.
上个月才见过 我们
Saw him just last month,we.
一起玩得很开心来着
Had a grand old time.
所以 怪不得之前都不见他
So,that's where he's been.
原来是去和人类开派对去了
Out partying with humans.
竟然还和猎魔人在一起
With hunters.
而我在这里独自凋零
While I languish here.
在这个破地方 做着这份不能杀人的鬼工作
In this go-nowhere,no-kill,joke-of-a-job.
开派对 有点夸张了
Partying is a bit of an exaggeration.
这份工作太恶心了
This job blows.
我不干了
I quit.
告诉我他们在哪里
Tell me where they are.
我说过了
I told you.
他们都死了
They are dead.
只剩我一个了
I'm the last.
你还看不出来吗 他说的是实话
Can't you see?He's telling the truth.
他都说了
He's done.
嗯 我知道
Yes,I believe he is.
现在把他干掉
Now finish him off.
Bartholomew 没必要这么做
Bartholomew,it doesn't need to be like this.
Castiel 看清现实吧
Castiel,get your head out of the sand.
你知道他们把你
You know why they brought you.
带出来的原因
Back from the battle field.
你知道真相
The truth.
是 我知道
Yeah,I know the truth.
我们的领导想让那些人死
Our leaders wanted those captives killed.
他们知道 你一定不会遵守命令
And they knew you'd stand away from their order.
说 你没那个本事
Said you didn't have it in you.
你做不到顾全大局
That you couldn't do what needed to be done.
但是我的看法不一样
But I know different.
- 我知道你变了 - 我不是杀人凶手
- I know you've changed - I'm not a murderer.
以前不是
You weren't,not then.
自从你杀了千万的天使
But since then you've slaughtered thousands of angels.
你杀了Malachi 夺取了他的荣光
You kill Malachi's man for his grace.
以前的我 以前我做过的事
Who I was,what I did.
与现在的我无关
That's not who I am.
是吗 那你到底是谁
No?Then who were you.
我想和你并肩作战 Castiel
I want to work with you,Castiel.
但是我需要证明
But I need proof.
他们需要证明他们错了
They need proof that they were wrong.
证明你可以顾全大局 完成任务
That you can do what has to be done.
你必须完成这个任务
This has to be done.
你一开始就没打算放我走
I was never free to leave.
我的选择中 只有遵守命令 或者被清除
My only choice was to obey or be killed.
我选
Well,I choose.
我很抱歉听到这个决定
I am truly sorry to hear that.
不
No.
你知道我已经多久
Do you know how long it's been.
没干过这个了吗
Since I've done this.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢让我想起来 我到底是谁
For reminding me what I truly am.
你拒绝得很清楚
As your refusal makes perfectly clear.
你一直觉得 你比我强
You always thought you're better than me.
我们是不是应该让你的上司来宣告这次的测试
Should we put your superior to order the test.
以绝后患
Once and for all.
不
No.
天使与天使之间的斗争
Angels fighting angels.
总归是要结束
Has to stop somewhere.
最好从我这儿开始
Might as well stop as me.
好吧
Fine.
别过来
Stand down.
这是我和叛徒间的战斗
This is between me and the rebel.
动手啊 赢家
Do it,victor.
来啊
Do it.
不
No.
你现在是怎么了
What are you now.
改过自新了
A penitent.
我什么也不是
I'm nothing.
你从来就没明白过 Castiel
You never did understand,Castiel.
没有流血 就没有和平
There can be no peace without blood shed.
让我走
Let me pass.
来啊 杀我啊
Do it.Kill me.
我们在等另一个人
No,we're saving you for someone else.
Crowley
Crowley.
更糟
Much worse.
把你交给Tran女士
Hand you out to Mrs.Tran.
乐意之极
With pleasure.
女士
Lady.
我发誓
I swear.
我只是服从命令
I was just following orders.
带我去找我儿子
Take me to my son.
Kevin你在吗
Kevin,you here.
Kev
Kev.
在
Well.
我们找到她了
We got her.
她还活着
She's alive.
她就在这儿
She's here.
我们想给你点儿时间
Now we want give you a moment to.
处理 你懂得
You know,process.
我怎么
How...I.
她知道吗
Does she know.
Kevin
Kevin.
我儿
My little son.
妈
Hey,mom.
这些
So this is.
全在这儿了
This is all of it.
只有猎人的工具 没有书
You know,hunters' tools,no books.
没有纸 没有笔
Papers,pencils.
有高考成绩
The SAT results.
考得真好
Perfect score.
你发现什么了吗
What do you get,kid.
这个
This.
是这个
This is it.
这是他父亲的
It's his father's.
Tran先生去世的时候
Mr.Tran died.
Kevin还在襁褓里
When Kevin was a baby.
这是Kevin对父亲
It's the only piece of father.
唯一的记忆
Kevin ever had.
如果Kevin的灵魂
If Kevin's spirit's.
附在什么东西上的话
Bound to some object here.
一定就是这个
This is it.
Tran夫人
Listen,Mrs.Tran.
我们对Kevin的情况
There's a lot we don't know.
还有很多不了解的地方
About Kevin's situation.
把他带回去
There're risks.
是有风险的
To take him home with you.
如果灵魂长时间停留在人世
The spirits,the longer that they are in the veil.
他们就会
They have a way of.
结果不太好
Well,it doesn't end up well.
他是我儿子
He's my son.
我的职责就是保证他的安全
It's my job to keep him safe.
只要我还活在这世上一天
For as long as I can.
很抱歉 我
Sorry I.
制造了这场混乱
Created this chaos.
很抱歉 我没能更好地解决问题
Sorry I couldn't do more to fix it.
你从表面上看
You may have.
是输了 Rebecca
Lost the war,Rebecca.
但是 你开辟了新的道路
But you tried a new way.
对此我深表尊敬
I have my respect for that.
我不想打
I don't wanna fight.
如果必要的话 我会的
But if I have to,I will.
我不知道来打架的
I didn't come to fight.
当我坠落的时候 我以为我没有别的选择
When I fell,I thought I had no choice.
但是昨天 你让我看到
But yesterday you showed me.
还有另一种选择
That there is a choice.
我决定追随你
And I choose you.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是领导者
I'm no leader.
不 你是
Yes,you are.
如果你要我 Castiel
If you have me,Castiel.
我会追随你
I will follow you.
我不是一个人
And I'm not the only one.
这几年来 她一直被折磨 都是因为我
She's held tortured for years because of me.
现在我们又在一起了
Now that I've found her.
我不会再让她离开我的视线
I'm not letting her out of my sight.
她是我的责任
She's my responsibility.
你是我们的责任
You are ours.
我让你失望了 我
I failed you.I.
Sam
Sam.
我知道那不是你
I know that wasn't you.
不然我当时有机会的话也会用刀杀了你的
Could have been a blade in that ass who possessed you.
就算扯平了吧
I'll call it a square.
那个
Guys.
谢谢
Thank you.
等我们把你送去
You can thank us when we.
你所属的天堂的时候 你再谢我们吧
Get you to heaven,where you belong.
这段时间
Okay?Until then.
好好跟妈妈待着
Enjoy the time with your mom.
享受无间断的 全天候
The uninterrupted 24/7.
不折不扣的亲子时间
No escape quality time.
混蛋
Dick.
我走之前
Hey,before I go.
答应我件事
You guys promise me something.
- 你说 - 随便什么都行
- Yeah - Anything.
你们俩
Can you two.
能和好吗
Get over it.
因为
It's.
你们看不见我
Just 'cause you can't see me.
我可看得见你们
Doesn't mean I can't see you.
一天吵来吵去不停
The drama,the fighting.
太蠢了
It's stupid.
我妈带回家一个灵魂
My mom's taking home a ghost.
你们
You two.
你们还都活生生的站在这儿
You're both still here.
当然
Of course.
答应你
Promise.
答应了
Yeah.
好
Good.
这可真是
Well,that was.
呃 好吧
Yeah, okay